groceryalerts.ca 2014-11-06

# Privacy Statement

**Information about Privacy on GroceryAlerts.ca**

GroceryAlerts.ca is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement only applies to GroceryAlerts.ca; it does not apply to other online or offline GroceryAlerts.ca sites, products or services. Please read the complete GroceryAlerts.ca privacy statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Personal information collected by GroceryAlerts.ca often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

GroceryAlerts.ca also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of GroceryAlerts.ca

GroceryAlerts.ca also collects information about which pages our customers visit within GroceryAlerts.ca. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique ID number, and it is never linked with personal information unless a user consents as described below.

**Unsubscribe Option**

You will have the option to unsubscribe (Opt-out) of all communications from our company, by clicking the ‘Unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of every email message we send or replying to the message with the word unsubscribe in the message body.

**Use of your Personal Information**

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To ensure our site is relevant to your needs.

  * To deliver services, such as newsletters, events, training or software, that you request or purchase.

  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.

  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate.

GroceryAlerts.ca may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on GroceryAlerts.ca or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of GroceryAlerts.ca and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of GroceryAlerts.ca employees, users of GroceryAlerts.ca products or services, or members of the public.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which GroceryAlerts.ca or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

GroceryAlerts.ca may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.

**Access to your Personal Information**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current.

**Security of your Personal Information and Credit Cards  
**

GroceryAlerts.ca is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Protection of Children’s Personal Information**

GroceryAlerts.ca is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

**Use of Cookies**

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer’s machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above.

We also use cookies to collect information on which newsletter links are clicked by customers. This information is used to ensure we are sending information customers want to read. It is collected in aggregate form and never linked with your personal information.

Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a GroceryAlerts.ca Web page. We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information on GroceryAlerts.ca; it is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about GroceryAlerts.ca Web site usage. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies but do not allow other companies to place clear gifs on our sites.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the GroceryAlerts.ca Web site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site.

**Changes to this Statement**

GroceryAlerts.ca will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, GroceryAlerts.ca will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.

**Author:[Lina Zussino](https://plus.google.com/100963511350484277872?rel=author)** on May 28th, 2011. Steven Zussino is the co-founder of Grocery Alerts Canada. He loves to help Canadians save money on groceries. He also runs the blog, CanadianPersonalFinance.com. 

**Want a travel Card that knows no boundaries?**

  * Earn a Welcome Bonus of 25,000 Membership Rewards points (worth $250) just by making $500 in purchases in your first 3 months of membership. That's enough for a round-trip flight almost anywhere in North America!
  * No annual fee for the first year. A value of $150!
  * Earn 2 points for every $1 in Card purchases at eligible gas stations, grocery stores and drugstores in Canada
  * Earn 2 points for every $1 in Card purchases for eligible travel purchases, including flights, hotels, car rentals, cruises, and more.
  * Earn one point for every $1 in Card purchases everywhere else.
  * Transfer your points to frequent flyer programs, or one-to-one to Aeroplan and Avios.
  * Charge any travel including gas to your Card and pay with points, with no blackout periods.
